A New Disney Holiday Featurette
Olaf's Frozen Adventure is a animation, family, adventure
film directed by Stevie Wermers-Skelton.
Olaf is on a mission to harness the best holiday
traditions for Anna, Elsa, and Kristoff.
Olaf (Voice), played by Josh Gad.
Anna (Voice), played by Kristen Bell.
Elsa (Voice), played by Idina Menzel.
Kristoff (voice), played by Jonathan Groff.
Young Elsa (voice), played by Eva Bella.
Oaken (voice), played by Chris Williams.
Olaf's Frozen Adventure is a 2017 American animated featurette produced by Walt
Disney Animation Studios and directed by Kevin Deters and Stevie Wermers.
The screenplay was written by Jac Schaeffer, with Josh Gad, Kristen Bell, Idina
Menzel, and Jonathan Groff reprising their roles from Frozen (2013).
In November 2017, Olaf's Frozen Adventure premiered in theaters for a limited-time engagement in 3D format
preceding the screening of Pixar's Coco and made its television debut on ABC in the following December.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
It was nominated for Best Animated Special Production, Outstanding Achievement for Animated Effects in an Animated
Production, and Outstanding Achievement for Music in an Animated Feature Production at the 45th Annie Awards.
The film explores themes of holiday, cartoon, musical, snowman, christmas.
The tone is lighthearted.